// Array of questions with options and correct answers
const questions = [
{
    numb: 221,
    question: 'Water source beneath the earth flowing naturally is called ____?',
    answer: 'Spring',
    options: [
      'Stream',
      'Fall',
      'Spring',
      'Lake'
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 222,
    question: 'What animal has the shortest gestation period known is 12 to 13 days?',
    answer: 'Opossum',
    options: [
      'Opossum',
      'Cat',
      'Elephant',
      'Mouse'
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 223,
    question: 'What approximate part of J&K is under India’s occupation?',
    answer: '75%',
    options: [
      '75%',
      '60%',
      '90%',
      '50%'
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 224,
    question: 'What are the Coldest months in Australia?',
    answer: 'July and August',
    options: [
      'December and January',
      'February and March',
      'July and August',
      'April and May'
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 225,
    question: 'What colour belt are martial arts experts entitled to wear?',
    answer: 'Black',
    options: [
      'Black',
      'Red',
      'White',
      'Green'
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 226,
    question: 'What do you mean by word “Android” ____?',
    answer: 'Human Like',
    options: [
      'Tough Animal',
      'Fast Eagle',
      'Human Like',
      'Tasty Food'
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 227,
    question: 'What does the Roman Numeral C represents?',
    answer: '100',
    options: [
      '1000',
      '100',
      '50',
      'None of the above'
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 228,
    question: 'What is a basin?',
    answer: 'Lower area of land',
    options: [
      'High area of land',
      'Deep area of River',
      'Lower area of land',
      'Deep area of ocean'
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 229,
    question: 'What is length of the Albert Canal?',
    answer: '80.5 mile',
    options: [
      '80.5 mile',
      '84 mile',
      '86 mile',
      'None'
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 230,
    question: 'What is the Currency of Mongolia?',
    answer: 'Togrog',
    options: [
      'Togrog',
      'Euro',
      'Piso',
      'Dollar'
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 231,
    question: 'What is the length of Ranikot fort?',
    answer: '31 kilometer, 19 (mi)',
    options: [
      '32 kilometer, 20 (mi)',
      '33 kilometer, 21 (mi)',
      '31 kilometer, 19 (mi)',
      '30 kilometer, 18 (mi)'
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 232,
    question: 'What is the most popular second language in the world?',
    answer: 'English',
    options: [
      'China',
      'Spanish',
      'English',
      'French'
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 233,
    question: 'What is the name of Capital of Nigeria?',
    answer: 'Abuja',
    options: [
      'Helsinki',
      'Niamey',
      'Abuja',
      'Ulaanbator'
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 234,
    question: 'What is the name of Europe’s first underwater restaurant?',
    answer: 'Under',
    options: [
      '5.8 Undersea Restaurant',
      'Ithaa Undersea Restaurant',
      'Under',
      'SEA'
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 235,
    question: 'What is the name of the storm which hit the United Kingdom in February 2020?',
    answer: 'Storm Dennis',
    options: [
      'Storm Habin',
      'Storm Kyar',
      'Storm Cirar',
      'Storm Dennis'
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 236,
    question: 'What is the name of world oldest Skydiver?',
    answer: 'Irene O’Shea',
    options: [
      'Irene O’Shea',
      'Ainy',
      'Jimmy',
      'Angela'
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 237,
    question: 'What is the total length of Indus River?',
    answer: '3180 km',
    options: [
      '2900 km',
      '2514 km',
      '3180 km',
      '7854 km'
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 238,
    question: 'What is the world’s largest living mammal?',
    answer: 'Blue Whale',
    options: [
      'Elephant',
      'Blue Whale',
      'Shark',
      'Giraffe'
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 239,
    question: 'What Kansas city’s name means ‘potato’ in the Kansa language?',
    answer: 'Topeka',
    options: [
      'Abeline',
      'Topeka',
      'Omaha',
      'Wichita'
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 240,
    question: 'What razor-thin country accounts for more than half of the western coastline of South America?',
    answer: 'Chile',
    options: [
      'Chile',
      'Peru',
      'Ecuador',
      'Colombia'
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 241,
    question: 'What was the first country to leave the United Nations?',
    answer: 'Indonesia',
    options: [
      'Iran',
      'Iraq',
      'Indonesia',
      'Greece'
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 242,
    question: 'What was the height of Quaid-e-Azam Mohammad Ali Jinnah, the founder of Pakistan?',
    answer: '5 feet & 10 inches',
    options: [
      '5 feet & 8 inches',
      '5 feet & 10 inches',
      '5 feet & 3 inches',
      '5 feet & 2 inches'
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 243,
    question: 'What was the name of Malaysian airline flight which was lost and disappeared in 2014?',
    answer: 'MH 370',
    options: [
      'MH 370',
      'MH 385',
      'NN 350',
      'MN 300'
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 244,
    question: 'What was the old name of Quetta?',
    answer: 'Shalkot',
    options: [
      'Karatshi',
      'Shalamar',
      'Shalkot',
      'Quetta'
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 245,
    question: 'When did Mongolian leader Temujin defeat his rivals and receive the title Genghis Khan, Universal Ruler of the Mongols?',
    answer: '1206',
    options: [
      '1205',
      '1206',
      '1207',
      'None of these'
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 246,
    question: 'When did the New York Stock Exchange open its first permanent headquarters near Wall Street in New York City?',
    answer: '4 January 1865',
    options: [
      '3 January 1865',
      '4 January 1865',
      '5 January 1877',
      '6 January 1879'
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 247,
    question: 'When did Tipu Sultan die?',
    answer: 'May 4, 1799',
    options: [
      'May 4, 1799',
      'May 4, 1899',
      'May 4, 1699',
      'None of these'
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 248,
    question: 'When was the International Olympic Committee established?',
    answer: '1894',
    options: [
      '1894',
      '1890',
      '1916',
      '1896'
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 249,
    question: 'When did the Iran-Iraq war end?',
    answer: 'August 20, 1988',
    options: [
      'August 20, 1986',
      'August 20, 1987',
      'August 20, 1988',
      'August 20, 1989'
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 250,
    question: 'When was the state of Israel established?',
    answer: '1948',
    options: [
      '1945',
      '1947',
      '1948',
      'None of these'
    ]
  }
  
]
